# **Loveneet Singh**

769-682-3218

chahal.loveneet@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/lovechahal

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A dynamic professional with 9+ years in the areas of experience in analysis, development, testing and implementation of various internet-based web applications using ASP.NET Core, ASP.Net MVC, Web Api, C#, Sql Server, MySql, JavaScript, JQuery, AngularJS, Angular, Typescript, MongoDb, Git, Jira, Bitbucket, SVN, ReactJS, NodeJS and Ionic Framework. Easily collaborate with developers and project manager to accomplish milestones. Professional objective to be a part of the dynamic software industry and contribute in creating high value solutions to challenging problems.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Senior Angular And .Net Developer

Jul 2021 - Present

**Evolvous Limited • Calgary** 

- Responsible for the quality and coding of software components that make up complex systems.
- · Performing low to medium complexity source code development.
- Testing software in controlled, real situations before it goes live.

Team Leader Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

Rivaire • Chandigarh

- Manage Team and Handle Team Problems.
- Responsible for the quality and coding of software components that make up complex systems.
- Involved in designing Database and Architecture

## **Assistant Team Leader**

Aug 2018 - Feb 2019

Osvin Web Solutions • Chandigarh

- · Manage Team with team leader.
- Developing the Code as per the requirements.
- Involved in developing the business logics, designing Database and Architecture.

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

Oct 2017 - Aug 2018

Ameba Technologies • Mohali

- · Risk and contingency planning.
- Investigating, diagnosing and correcting system issues.
- Testing software in controlled, real situations before it goes live.

.Net Developer Apr 2016 - Jan 2017

Matrix Solutions • Chandigarh

Design, write, read, test, and correct code for new software

 Analyze information to recommend and plan the installation of new systems or modifications of an existing system

# . Net Developer

Jul 2013 - Dec 2015

Soft Solutions India • Chandigarh

- · Working as an intern.
- · Working alongside wider operational teams to achieve set goals
- Design, write, read, test, and correct code for new software and applications

# **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of technology**

Aug 2009 - Sep 2013

Punjab Technical University • Jalandhar

I have done my graduation (B-Tech in Information Technology) from Global Institutes of Management & Emerging Technologies, Amritsar under Punjab Technical University

# **SKILLS**

Self Starter, Problem solving, Organizational skills, Risk Management, Multitasking, Teamwork